[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American fashion designer is widely recognized as the creator of the American Look.", "correct_answer": "Claire McCardell", "incorrect_answers": ["Elsa Schiaperelli", "James Mainbocher", "Hattie Carnegie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If bactrian equals two, what equals one?", "correct_answer": "Dromedary", "incorrect_answers": ["Diamond", "Daschund", "Dynasty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The comic books The Adventures of Asterix focus on the exploits of a village of ancient Gauls as they resist Greek occupation.", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2001 animated comedy movie Shrek, the donkey falls in love with what character?", "correct_answer": "Dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["One of the three pigs", "Pinocchio", "The Big Bad Wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1971 science fiction movie A Clockwork Orange, which voted the fourth best science fiction movie by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Stanley Kubrick", "incorrect_answers": ["Ridley Scott", "Steven Spielberg", "Martin Scorsese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these ladies played the role of Shelby Eatenton-Latcherie in the movie Steel Magnolias?", "correct_answer": "Julia Roberts", "incorrect_answers": ["Dolly Parton", "Daryl Hannah", "Sally Feild"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Drosera, an insectivorous plant that grows in South Africa, South America and Australia, attracts the insects to its tips in what way?", "correct_answer": "By its dew-drop appearance", "incorrect_answers": ["By its colours", "By its smell of rotting meat", "By its sweet smell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fact about Gaylord does little Jack find very amusing in the 2004 comedy movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "That he is a nurse", "incorrect_answers": ["That he came out in 9th place in some competition", "His name", "His big ears"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert De Nero starred as a priest in the movie Sleepers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Flower tiles are not necessary to win a hand in a classic Mahjong game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is General George Patton buried?", "correct_answer": "Luxembourg", "incorrect_answers": ["Normandy, France", "Arlington National Cemetery", "Washington, D.C."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Female mantes (the plural for mantis) are larger than males.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]